Why are you
being so nervous?
It's me who
made the mistake
No
Should you not
go see Shin Yoo-il?
Yoo-il told me
to see you first
What happened?
Hello everyone
long time no see
[Hell TV]
[Neighborhood Gym Tour]
Oh my
[Isn't that Shin Yoo-il?
Wait, it's really him!]
I asked him when he'd
break up with you
saying it was wrong
from the beginning
Then, he asked me back
if I was obsessed
with you
because of what
happened in the past
What happened
in the past?
Back then…
when you
were trapped
in a warehouse
the kid who stayed
with you there
was Shin Yoo-il
The kid who used to come
to see you every day…
It was
Shin Yoo-il
I knew you were
misunderstanding
I felt guilty
every time
I was bragging
that I saved your life
But I lied
to stay next to you
using that
I mean
Shin Yoo-il wasn't wrong
He stayed with me
until I was saved
No, that's not true…